I let out a huge sigh into the overcast sky
ドンヨリした空に　思いきり溜息ひとつ
It feels like I’m being driven by unrelenting pressure (like I’m being swallowed by it)
勝ち気なプレッシャ — に追い込まれそう(飲み込まれそう)
Ah, this is a very major step
Ah　超重要なステップ
Too absorbed in that, I rushed away
夢中になり過ぎてすっ飛ばした
Aggravating my impatience even worse, I stay sulky (A self-sabotaging attitude)
歯がゆさこじらせて　ふてくされ中(損なAttitude)
It’s just as I thought, I’m still being spoiled by you
やっぱり　まだキミに甘えてる
I can’t win against myself like this
こんな調子じゃ　自分に勝てない
I’ll break out of my shell this instant
今すぐこの殻を打ち破って
And go look for shards of glimmer
キラメキのかけら探すんだ
That’s not to say that I’m no longer wavering,
もう迷いがない訳じゃない
But I’m moving ahead, even so!
それでも進むよ！
You, who seem to give off light
ひたすら　さりげない優しさで
With an off-the-cuff kindness that comes from the bottom of your heart—
光を照らすようなキミが
You simply believe
ただ　可能性のつぼみを
In this bud of potential, so
信じてくれるから
Please watch
見ていてね
My starry days☆
私の Starry Days☆
When I’m given a sudden task, my contrarian soul gets flustered
突然の使命に　あまのじゃく魂(だましい)　どぎまぎ
Why do I pointlessly try to look cool? (My personality gets weird)
ど — してか　無駄にカッコつけちゃう(キャラ変しちゃう)
Ah, I threw out too many ad-libbed remarks
Ah　アドリブかまし過ぎて
And get called to the teachers’ office again
また職員室に呼び出された
Struggling with all my might to get high praise (A girl’s etude)
シャカリキに大絶賛(だいぜっさん)奮闘中(ふんとうちゅう)(オトメのetude)
As expected, once again I’ve caused trouble for you
やっぱり　またキミを困らせた
At the very least, I want to become able to be frank with you in times like these
こんな時ぐらい　素直になりたい
Once two or more racing hearts are gathered together,
ひとたび　ドキドキが集まれば
Infinite dreams burst into giddiness
∞(むげん)の夢がはしゃぎ出す
Even if they’re all subjects I’m still bad at,
まだ苦手科目ばっかでも
I can’t sit still!
じっとしていられないよ！
As this fluffy, tickling affection
モコモコ　くすぐったい愛情が
Grows bigger and bigger, filling up my heart
胸いっぱいに　ふくらんで
I’ll convey it to you with everything I’ve got,
この息を止めてしまう前に
Before I wind up just holding my breath
思い切り伝えるから
So please look at
見ていてね
My shy starry smile☆
ハニカミ Starry Smile☆
Hey, whenever I gaze at you,
キミのこと見つめるたびに　ねぇ
I realize my true feelings
気づいたよ　本当のキモチ
Embracing this self that wants to become steadfast and unwavering
揺るがない　なりたい自分
Tight, tight
強く　強く　抱(いだ)いて
Whenever I spot that face,
いつでもその顔を見つけたら
My world always suddenly starts dancing
世界が急に踊りだす
Look! As the flowers of our smiles bloom
ほら　笑顔の花が咲いて
Our hearts are connected
心　繋がるよ
You, who seem to give off light
ひたすら　さりげない優しさで
With an off-the-cuff kindness that comes from the bottom of your heart—
光を照らすようなキミが
You simply believe
ただ　可能性のつぼみを
In this bud of potential, so
信じてくれるから
Please watch
見ていてね
My starry days☆
私の Starry Days☆